So if we treat fragments as mini activities, each with
its own independent life cycle in UI, how does that compare
to the life cycle of a real activity? Well as
you might expect the basic life cycle events are much the
same as the parent activity, and as it moves through
the cycles of starts, resumes, pauses, and stops those same life
cycle events will be triggered within the fragment itself. So,
in most cases, you can simply move anything that you would
have put into the activities life cycle handles,
into the corresponding fragment handles. With, of course, a
couple of exceptions. Rather than building your UI here
and onCreate, fragments introduced a new event specifically for
this. OnCreate view is where you construct or inflate
your UI, hook up to any data sources, and
return it to the parent activity, which can then
integrate it into its view hierarchy. There's a corresponding
onDestroy view handler, which is called immediately before the
fragment is added to the backstack, independent of the
parent activity. Now keep in mind that the fragment
manager can add any fragment transactions adding, removing, or replacing
fragments to the back stack, with a single parent
activity's actives. So a fragment can move through this
cycle multiple times independent of the host activity. So
onDestroy view is, where you should clean up any resources,
specifically related to the UI, such as bitmaps in
memory, cursors to data, anything like that to help ensure
that your app's memory footprint isn't bloated by data that's
not needed when the fragment isn't visible. Now as soon
as the fragment is returned from the back stack, onCreate
view is called, and you can re-create the UI and
reconnect data sources before your fragment transitions through the rest
of the life cycle to become active again. And because
a fragment can only exist within an activity,
we also need callbacks to tell us when a
fragment is attached and detached from its parent. OnAttach
is your opportunity to get a reference to the
parent activity. While, onDetach is the last thing that
happens, even after your fragment has technically been destroyed.
Now, the final piece of the puzzle is onActivity
created. This notifies our fragment that the parent activity
has completed its own create handler and represents the point
at which we can safely interact with its UI. Potentially
including other fragments. Now, just like the activity lifecyle we
discussed in lesson three, once the fragment is no longer
visible, there's a chance it will be terminated with no
further code being executed. That can happen, after onStop, in
the case of the activity being terminated while the fragment
is part of that activity's view hierarchy, or after onDestroy
view, if the fragment has already been placed
in the back stack, once the activity is destroyed.